sapub.org 2017-12-15

# Scientific & Academic Publishing: Privacy policy

##  Privacy policy

We respect your privacy and are committed to ensuring that your personal information is safeguarded. This Website defines the ways in which we use, collect and protect the information that you provide when using our Website. While using this Website you are accepting the practices stated in this Privacy Policy.

There are several circumstances on this Website in which you may be asked to submit information from which you can be identified. Make sure that all information collected will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

###  Personal Information

There are several instances in which we may collect information from you. We may collect personal information that you provide to us such as name, telephone number, e-mail and postal address. Based on the information you provide, we may contact you to respond to your inquiries, discuss products, service or purchases. Access to your personal information is only restricted to our employees, agents, representatives, service providers, and entities for which we are acting as an agent, licensee or publisher, such as societies, for the purposes set forth above. Aside from these organizations, we will not disclose, distribute or sell your personal information to other third parties unless we have your prior permission or are required by law to do so.

###  Automatic Statistics Information

We also collect non-personal information from you such as web browser type and version, Uniform Resource Locator (URL) of the previous Website visited, Internet Service Provider (ISP), operating system, cookies and Internet protocol (IP) address. 

###  Security

We take every reasonable measure necessary and continue to make high-quality safety to protect the privacy and integrity of our customers’ personal information while providing the high level communication services they expect. We follow accepted industry standards to protect the information you submit to us, both in transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of Internet transmission and electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your information, we cannot guarantee absolute security. We retain the personal information we collect from you for as long as the information is relevant to the fulfillment of our business purposes or until you request that we remove the data.

We reserve the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for updates and changes. This policy is effective on May 20, 2012.

If you believe any of the information we have about you is incomplete or incorrect, please contact us. We will promptly correct any inaccurate information. If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, please contact us at [service@sapub.org](mailto:service@sapub.org)

Just enter your email address below,we will share with you the latest information of journals published by SAP. Plus, you can easily unsubscribe at any time, and we'll never share your email address with anyone.
